IGNACIO SANTANA

Junior QA Analyst, Smartbox

E: nacho.sanmor@gmail.com LinkedIn: ie.linkedin.com/in/ignacio-santana-morales M: +353 (0) 834535917

PROFILE

Junior QA Analyst in Smartbox group, Dublin. Currently studying a Fullstack Web Development course from the Code Institute. Familiar with working in diverse teams and projects across Smartbox over the last three years. I'm passionate about learning and developing my skillset to ensure I remain up-to-date and adapt with new and ever changing technologies.

LANGUAGES

Fluent English speaker and native Spanish speaker.

EDUCATION

May 2018 **CEFR Level C1 in English**, IELTS Academic

June 2011 Professional Diploma in Business Finances, Felo Monzón, Gran Canaria, Spain

CORE MODULES IN THE COURSE

1.Programming Paradigms	2.HTML Fundamentals	3.CSS Fundamentals
4.User Centric Frontend Development	5.JavaScript Fundamentals	6.Interactive Frontend Development
7.Python Fundamental	8.Practical Python	9.Data Centric Development
10.Full Stack Frameworks with Django		

CAREER SUMMARY

SmartboxJunior QA AnalystJan 2020- PresentSmartboxApplication SupportJun 2018 – Jan 2020SmartboxAccount ManagerNov 2017 – Jun 2018SmartboxSales RepresentativeMarch 2017 – Nov 2017Nando's, Mary StSupervisorOct 2016 – Mar 2017

WORK HISTORY

Junior QA Analyst | Smartbox

The team works with the developers to ensure the quality and functionality of the different systems and application in Smartbox.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Participate fully in Agile SDLC (Story Grooming, Estimation, Retro, Standup etc)
- Test definition & design using Test Case Management Tool (Xray, BDD)
- Feature & Bug Validation
- Ran manual regression tests for every feature tested
- Strong communication & collaboration with project stakeholders (PO, Dev & QA)
- Supported frequent software releases to production

Application Support | Smartbox

The team's core function is to provide application support across all Smartbox departments by fielding queries and issues and collaborating with teams to resolve outstanding problems.

ACHIEVEMENTS

• Provided assistance to the SalesForce team by assisting in a project aimed at promoting data accuracy enhance the overall customer sign-on process while using the SalesForce software.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Responsible for providing in-house support and trouble-shooting of 27 applications across all departments.
- Understanding the cause of key issues, how the applications interact with each other and reporting the findings to the relevant teams.
- Develop procedures based on these findings and ensure the Application Support team is provided training by same.
- Running regular update meetings with key department heads such as the Application and Product Owners.

PROJECT

• Desktop Support

The team is responsible for new staff set-up, desktop and software installations and providing user support.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- One month secondment assisting the team covering a temporary team shortage.
- Installing software and desktop/laptop equipment to all employees.
- Providing user support to employees across all departments.

Account Manager | Smartbox

The Account Management team manages the relationships of all accounts in the Spanish market portfolio.

ACHIEVEMENTS

• Increased overall upselling numbers by researching and creating a report of potential products and partners to target. Developing complimentary documentation which outlines the ideal conversation starter tips for these potential partners to the team.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Working closely with my clients on their Key Accounts, enabling them to strategically set and achieve their revenue goals.
- Responsible for managing the relationships of over 600 accounts within a large portfolio in the Spanish market.
- Developing new processes to improve team efficiency and communication across various departments.
- Translating and copywriting the communication channels across Smartbox, varying from client correspondence, legal documentation and cross-departmental communication.

Sales Representative | Smartbox

The Sales team creates relationships with potential partners in the Spanish market.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Searching for possible leads, through web scraping, to create and develop positive working relationships with potential hospitality partners.
- Communicating daily with potential clients by cold calls and emails. Able to interact with a multitude of different personalities, always remaining professional and representing the firm values effectively.
- Able to control all the processes involved from the sales process to creating the contracts using the Sales Force software system. Following up by sending on the finalised copy to the client for their signature and relevant information.
- Continuously working through set targets monthly.
- Performing cost--benefit and needs analysis of existing/potential customers to meet their needs.
- Attending multiple business meetings weekly for training and up-skilling purposes. Able to adapt to the necessary changes in the sales process continuously due to the scale of company growth over a short period.

Supervisor | Nando's, Mary St

Customer Orientation & Problem Solving

- Excellent customer service in delivering a warm, genuine and memorable experience to the clientele.
- Ability to communicate with guests and employees, some of whom will require high levels of empathy, patience and diplomacy to defuse anger and to collect accurate information to resolve any potential issues.
- Competent in dealing with customer complaints on the floor, over the phone, e-mail and social media.

Teamwork and Collaboration

- Team coordination through management collaboration with staff on the floor, back of the house (kitchen) and deliveries
- High level of communication with area and int. Managers

Financial and Product Management

- Ability to set targets with clear standards and timescales and control of budget, orders and sales.
- Responsible for daily and monthly reports which are detailed and submitted in a timely matter.
- General upkeep and maintenance of equipment handling by calling for repair and training staff on proper use. Always using proper standard operating procedures to report and fix these issues.

SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES

- Completed first aid training
- Competent in ECDL Microsoft Word, Excel, Powerpoint
- Full European driving licence.
- Great communication skills
- Ability to handle multiple tasks in a dynamic environment.
- Highly motivated and enthusiastic team player
- Committed, reliable, trustworthy, positive and flexible.
- Awarded second place in the National Spanish Kickboxing competition 2011

REFERENCES ON REQUEST